ABDUL WASE

+91-7700931827 ♦ wasekhan558@gmail.com ♦ LinkedIn ♦ GitHub

1 year of experience in FinTech (Blockchain) with expertise in Crypto's & other ledger technologies. Possesses a highly analytical mindset, strong communication & relentless dedication to continuous iteration & improvement.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UltraTech June 2022 - Aug 2022 Product Manager Intern Mumbai, India

Analyzed the issues faced by 100+ vendors & dealers such as invoice, product SKU, payment gateway.

- · Collaborated with the technical team to diagnose and resolve 20+ software bugs within 4 weeks.
- · Contributed to the ongoing strategy, design and implementation of the portal that bridges both parties.

FNetwork July 2021 – June 2022 Blockchain Developer Delhi, India (Remote)

· Worked alongside with the team to develop a decentralized application along with native ERC20 token.

- · Conducted extensive testing of the smart contract on Polygon Main-net; achieved 100% test coverage and decreased risk of security vulnerabilities.
- · Collaborated with the Tech team to optimize website load time; conducted A/B testing and reduced page load time by 2 seconds, resulting in a 30% increase in page views.

Sept 2020 - Feb 2021 Accornet Mumbai, India

Front End Developer Intern

- · Independently wrote 150+ lines of code for the front-end of the website.
- Recruited 3 member and performed brainstorming activities daily on new UI templates.
- · Contributed to the team by collecting data-sets and performed scrapping for projects.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology in Information Technology

K.J Somaiya College of Engineering – University of Mumbai 2019 – 2023 | Mumbai, India

CGPA: 8.4

Senior Secondary (Physics, Chemistry, Mathematics & IT)

Thakur College of Science & Commerce 2016 – 2018 | Mumbai, India

Blockchain Developer Bootcamp Certification – Dapp University

SKILLS

Programming: Solidity, Python, Javascript, React, HTML, CSS Software: Jira, Excel, PowerPoint, SharePoint, LaTex

Tools: Git/GitHub, Google Cloud, IPFS, Ganache, Remix, VSCode, Infura

PROJECTS

Podium Decentralized Exchange - GitHub AvaxQueen NFT Game - GitHub Patient Health Record Blockchain - GitHub NFT Marketplace - GitHub

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Started a digital marketing company while in college and successfully worked with 3 E-com Client.
- Published 8 Crypto articles on Medium with over 100k views.